Brandi N Peters

678-203-5404

petersbn@gmail.com

brandi-n-peters

bnicp

SUMMARY

Resourceful, reliable, hard-working professional with 10+ years successful remote work roles. Knowledgeable across multiple industries and has leadership and management experience with direct reports. Excellent with new technologies and a quick learner of software and processes.



EXPERIENCE

Systems Consultant | Beep Co, LLC - Alpharetta, GA

2020-Present

- Consults with RE agents and clients on the systems they have in place for business efficiency
- Recommends technologies to implement for automation so they can focus on sales
- Includes writing content for home listings and custom business website builds

Systems Coach | LOCAL Realty / Red Barn Real Estate

2019-2021

- Conducted new agent onboarding, systems input, and user account creation
- Administrator for all company technology, including Google Workspace
- Consulted with agents about the individual systems in place for their personal sales businesses

Manager, Collections | Previously- Collections Team Lead, Asset Manager, Asset Performance Specialist | CAN Capital, Inc. - Kennesaw, GA 2015 - 2018

- partnered with business analytics on SSRS reporting to achieve streamlined processes
- coordinated with IT to verify root causes of system errors and tested bug fixes
- oversaw a portfolio in excess of \$20,000,000 worked by 3-5 agents
- executed cost analysis for under performing assets and forecasted monthly revenue and loss

Web Content Creator | Proxy Server, LLC - Remote, GA

2014

- Created and curated content for math curriculum and social sharing sites
- Wrote and implemented multi-level curriculum and FAQs
- Utilized HTML for formatting and presentation on each Wordpress page



RECENT PROJECTS

FDA Recalls Near Me | 2022

Contributed HTML and CSS framework (W3.CSS) to a site for consumers to retrieve information regarding FDA recalls. Link to deployed app on GitHub: https://bnicp.github.io/recall-near-me/

Password Generator | 2022

Web app to generate strong and random passwords with multiple parameter options. Link to deployed app on GitHub: https://bnicp.github.io/hw3-password-generator/

JavaScript Quiz | 2022

Quiz app with easily editable questions. Alerts correct or incorrect answers and stores high scores. Link to deployed app on GitHub: https://bnicp.github.io/hw4-javascript-quiz/



EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts in Business Administration | University of Florida, 2004
Full-stack Web Development Professional Certification | Georgia Institute of Technology, 2022



SKILLS

- Microsoft Office
- Cross-functional Collaboration
- HTML5
- Bootstrap
- Git
- Github

- Process Innovation
- Training
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Node.js
- jQuery